Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- L, 10738
  - Lippman, undated; cuid1654; 10801 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Litt, Benjamin, undated; cuid1655; 10802 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Littlejohn, Lomax, undated; cuid1656; 10803 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Liwschitz-Garik [?], 1942; cuid1657; 10804 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Lobenberg, Michel, undated; cuid1658; 10805 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Loebl, Ernest M., undated; cuid1659; 10806 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Lombarden, undated; cuid1660; 10807 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Lombardino, Joseph G., undated; cuid1661; 10808 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Lombardo, George A., undated; cuid1662; 10809 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Lord, Thomas, circa 1987; cuid1663; 10810 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Lorenz, Patricia A., 1998; cuid1664; 10811 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Low, Seth, circa 1866; cuid1665; 10812 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Lowe, Bill, undated; cuid1666; 10813 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Lowe, Helen, undated; cuid1667; 10814 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Lu, I-Tai, undated; cuid1668; 10815 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Lubell, Peter, 2001; cuid1669; 10816 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Luna, Anthony, undated; cuid1670; 10817 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Lundberg, Robert, undated; cuid1671; 10818 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Luntey, Eugene H., undated; cuid1672; 10819 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Lurie, Harold, 1979; cuid1673; 10820 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Lutwak, Erwin, undated; cuid1674; 10821 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Lutwick, Larry, undated; cuid1675; 10822 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Lybeck, Al, undated; cuid1676; 10823 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Lynch, James E., 1960; cuid1677; 10824 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Lynch, Patrick "Pat", undated; cuid1678; 10825 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Lynch, William A., undated; cuid1679; 10826 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Lynford, Jeffrey, undated; cuid1680; 10827 (Box 5, Folder 114)
- M, 10828
  - MacDiarmid, Alan G., undated; cuid1681; 10829 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - MacDonald, Kathleen, undated; cuid1682; 10830 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - MacDuff, John N., undated; cuid1683; 10831 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Maciag, Robert J., 1986, 1993; cuid1684; 10832 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Mack, Edward, circa 1905; cuid1685; 10833 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - MacKenzie, Lt. Col. F., 1968; cuid1686; 10834 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Maggio, Edward, undated; cuid1687; 10835 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Maillacheruvu, Krishnanand Y. "Kris", undated; cuid1688; 10836 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Mainiero, Michael, undated; cuid1689; 10837 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Malament, undated; cuid1690; 10838 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Maloof, Roula, undated; cuid1691; 10839 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Mancuso, Michael Jr., undated; cuid1692; 10840 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Mandelbaum, Richard, circa 1993; cuid1693; 10841 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Mandl, undated; cuid1694; 10842 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Manniello, John B. Louis, 1972; cuid1695; 10843 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Mansfield, Joseph, circa 1964; cuid1696; 10844 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Marchesi, W., undated; cuid1697; 10845 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Marchi, undated; cuid1698; 10846 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Marcus, Rudolph A., 1999; cuid1699; 10847 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Marcuvitz, Nathan, 1986; cuid1700; 10848 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Marder, Arnold R., 1974, 1981; cuid1701; 10849 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Mardus, Fred and Edna, 1980; cuid1702; 10850 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Margolin, Harold, undated; cuid1703; 10851 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Mark, Hans, 1982; cuid1704; 10852 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Mark, Herman: See Herman Mark Collection, undated; cuid1705; 10853
  - Markowitz, David, undated; cuid1706; 10854 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Marks, James "Buck", circa 1996; cuid1707; 10855 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Marks, Leonard, undated; cuid1708; 10857 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Marks, Sylvia K., undated; cuid1709; 10864 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Marschhausen, George W., undated; cuid1710; 10865 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Marshall, Gillian P., undated; cuid1711; 10866 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Marshall, John F., undated; cuid1712; 10867 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Martcheva, Maia, undated; cuid1713; 10868 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Martin, Harold E., undated; cuid1714; 10869 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Martinez, Arthur C., 1996; cuid1715; 10870 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Martini, Joseph, undated; cuid1716; 10871 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Martinovich, Betty, undated; cuid1717; 10872 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Martucci, Charles, undated; cuid1718; 10873 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Mason, Roger, undated; cuid1719; 10874 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Masaryk, Jan, 1941; cuid1720; 10875 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Masselos, William, undated; cuid1721; 10876 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Massey, Walter E., 2000; cuid1722; 10877 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Mastronardi, circa 1975; cuid1723; 10888 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Matalon, Moshe, 1978; cuid1724; 10889 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Match, Robert K., undated; cuid1725; 10890 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Matsuoka, Shiro, undated; cuid1726; 10891 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Matthews, Craig C., undated; cuid1727; 10892 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Mattiello, Joseph J., undated; cuid1728; 10893 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1985; cuid1729; 10894 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - May, William F., 1980; cuid1730; 10895 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Mayo, John S., undated; cuid1731; 10896 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Mazziota, Daniel, undated; cuid1732; 10959 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Mazzucco, Salvatore, 1975; cuid1733; 10897 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - McCabe, Warren L., 1950, 1954, 1955, 1961; cuid1734; 10898 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - McCauley [?], undated; cuid1735; 10899 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - McDonald, undated; cuid1736; 10900 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - McDonald, JoAnn, undated; cuid1737; 10901 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - McGinnis, Frank, undated; cuid1738; 10902 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - McIlveen, Edward E., undated; cuid1739; 10903 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - McKeen, John E., 1955; cuid1740; 10904 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - McLaughlin, Patricia A., 1999; cuid1741; 10905 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - McLean, Noel, undated; cuid1742; 10906 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - McNear, Cheryl, undated; cuid1743; 10907 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - McShane, William, 1986; cuid1744; 10908 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Mead, undated; cuid1745; 10909 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Meglino, Bruce M., undated; cuid1746; 10910 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Meinhold, Artie, 1942, 1950, 1955; cuid1747; 10911 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Meinhold, Herbert, undated; cuid1748; 10912 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Meites, Lou, undated; cuid1749; 10913 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Memon, Nasir, undated; cuid1750; 10914 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Menashe, Louis, undated; cuid1751; 10915 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Mendik, undated; cuid1752; 10916 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Mermelstein, David, 2002; cuid1753; 10917 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Mesrobian, Robert B., 1955; cuid1754; 10918 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Messerschmitt, Richard, circa 1996; cuid1755; 10919 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Messina, Philip, undated; cuid1756; 10920 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Meyer, Leonard S., undated; cuid1757; 10921 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Meyers, Bernard L., undated; cuid1758; 10922 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Michels, Frank G., undated; cuid1759; 10923 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Middendorf, Henry Q., 1956, 1967, 1970; cuid1760; 10924 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Midgette, Ernst L., 1954; cuid1761; 10925 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Mijovic, Jovan, 1986; cuid1762; 10960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Milas, Alfred, undated; cuid1763; 10961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Milgram, Joseph B. Jr., undated; cuid1764; 10962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Edward, undated; cuid1765; 10963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Irving F., 1964; cuid1766; 10964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Miller, J., undated; cuid1767; 10965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Wharton, undated; cuid1768; 10966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Miller, William T., undated; cuid1769; 10967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Millet, Marcus J., undated; cuid1770; 10968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mishkin, E., undated; cuid1771; 10969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Mishuck, Eli, 1975; cuid1772; 10970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Misra, Asoka, undated; cuid1773; 10971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, William, undated; cuid1774; 10972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mitnitsky, Samuel, undated; cuid1775; 10973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Molof, Alan H., 1983; cuid1776; 10974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mones, Arthur H., 1974; cuid1777; 10975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Montrone, undated; cuid1778; 10976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Moore, George E., 1964; cuid1779; 10977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Moore, Robert J., 1941; cuid1780; 10978 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Morancie, Horace L., undated; cuid1781; 10979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Morawetz, Herbert, 1978, 1981, 1995, 2001; cuid1782; 10980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Morduchow, Morris, 1978; cuid1783; 10981 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Morris, Philip, 2001; cuid1784; 10982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Morrison, Alexander W., undated; cuid1785; 10983 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Moslon, Julie, 1983; cuid1786; 10984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Motzkin, Shirley, 1971, 1994; cuid1787; 10985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Mow, William C. W., undated; cuid1788; 10986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Moy, Kirsten S., undated; cuid1789; 10987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, undated; cuid1790; 10988 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Mueller, Wheeler, 1978; cuid1791; 10989 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Mugglin, David, undated; cuid1792; 10990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Mukherjee, Kalinath, 1971; cuid1793; 10991 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mukhopadhay, Sharmila M., undated; cuid1794; 10992 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Mulcahy, David F., undated; cuid1795; 10993 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mulkin, undated; cuid1796; 10994 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Muller, F., undated; cuid1797; 10995 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Muller, S. H., undated; cuid1798; 10996 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Murawski, Thomas, 1973; cuid1799; 10997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Murphy, Donald, undated; cuid1800; 10998 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Murray, 1954; cuid1801; 10999 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Murray, Robt T.K., undated; cuid1802; 11000 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Murray, R. William, 1994; cuid1803; 11001 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Muss, Jonathan, 1990s; cuid1804; 11002 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Myers, Robert J., undated; cuid1805; 11003 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Myerson, Allan, 1994; cuid1806; 11004 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- N, 11005
  - Nader, Ralph, undated; cuid1807; 11006 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Nadro, Edward Jr., undated; cuid1808; 11007 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Naevestad, Roy, undated; cuid1809; 11008 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Nagler, Stewart G., 1985, 1993, 2000; cuid1810; 11009 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Nagy, William, undated; cuid1811; 11010 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Nakahara, Tsuneo, 1994; cuid1812; 11011 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Napoli, Rudolph P., undated; cuid1813; 11012 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Naumovich, Gleb, undated; cuid1814; 11013 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Nelson, Ed, undated; cuid1815; 11014 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Nelson, Richard E., undated; cuid1816; 11015 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Nelson, Theodore W., circa 1978; cuid1817; 11016 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Nespoli, Paolo A., 1999; cuid1818; 11017 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Neugebauer, George H., undated; cuid1819; 11018 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Newman, Joseph H., undated; cuid1820; 11019 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Newstein, Maurice C., undated; cuid1821; 11020 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Newton, Harry, undated; cuid1822; 11021 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Nickelson, Stanley, 1973; cuid1823; 11022 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Nicks, Oran W., undated; cuid1824; 11023 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Nielsen, John P., 1985; cuid1825; 11024 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Nies, Nelson, 1938; cuid1826; 11025 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Nijhawan, Ramesh K., 1974; cuid1827; 11026 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Nisenson, Stan, undated; cuid1828; 11027 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Noetzel, undated; cuid1829; 11028 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Nomovetsky, Frederick, undated; cuid1830; 11029 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Nones, Allan S., undated; cuid1831; 11030 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Norton, Richard A., Col., undated; cuid1832; 11031 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Nourbakhsh, Said, 1986, 2000; cuid1833; 11032 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Novomestky, Frederick, undated; cuid1834; 11033 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Nowak, Theodore, undated; cuid1835; 11034 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Nulty, Thomas, undated; cuid1836; 11035 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Nummy, W.R., undated; cuid1837; 11036 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Nyquist, Ewald B., undated; cuid1838; 11037 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- O, 11038
  - Obeid, Diya, 2000; cuid1839; 11039 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Obermeyer, Charles, 1954; cuid1840; 11040 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - O'Connell. Liam P.F., circa 1974; cuid1841; 11041 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - O'Connor, Arthur M., 1956; cuid1842; 11042 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - O'Connor, John J., 1954, 1955; cuid1843; 11043 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - O'Dea, Tom, undated; cuid1844; 11044 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Oergel, Charles T., 1955; cuid1845; 11045 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Oguchi, Bunichi, circa 1996; cuid1846; 11046 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Okamoto, Yoshiyuki, undated; cuid1847; 11047 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - O'Leary, Hazel R., undated; cuid1848; 11048 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Oleck, John, undated; cuid1849; 11049 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Olexson, Gerard, circa 1974; cuid1850; 11050 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Oliner, Arthur A., 1967; cuid1851; 11051 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Olpin, A.R., undated; cuid1852; 11052 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Olsen, John C., circa 1937, 1952; cuid1853; 11053 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Olshan, Kenneth S., 1990s; cuid1854; 11054 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Omoagbi, Paul, undated; cuid1855; 11055 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Ooro, Otieno, undated; cuid1856; 11056 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Oppenheim, Alan and Rosa, circa 1998; cuid1857; 11057 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Orden, C.J., undated; cuid1858; 11058 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - O'Rourke, Kevin, undated; cuid1859; 11059 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Orso, Camillo A., circa 1997; cuid1860; 11060 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Osborne, undated; cuid1861; 11061 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Oster, Gerald, undated; cuid1862; 11062 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Othmer, Donald, 1976; cuid1863; 11063 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Othmer, Mildred Topp, undated; cuid1864; 11064 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Otugen, M. Volkan, undated; cuid1865; 11065 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Oussani, James, undated; cuid1866; 11066 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Overberger, Charles G., 1952, 1955; cuid1867; 11067 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Overstreet, Jamahl W., undated; cuid1868; 11068 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Owades, Joseph L., 1999; cuid1869; 11069 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Owens, Major, 1999; cuid1870; 11070 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Oxman, Jack, undated; cuid1871; 11071 (Box 6, Folder 110)
- P, 11072
  - Pace, Norma, undated; cuid1872; 11073 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Pack, Arthur, undated; cuid1873; 11074 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Packard, David, undated; cuid1874; 11075 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Paczkowski, Henry C., undated; cuid1875; 11076 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Padavan, Frank, undated; cuid1876; 11077 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Padro, Dianne, undated; cuid1877; 11078 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Paige, Clifford E., undated; cuid1878; 11079 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Palchefsky, John, undated; cuid1879; 11080 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Pallo, Joseph S., undated; cuid1880; 11081 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Palmer, Charles, 1997; cuid1881; 11082 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Palocz, Istvan, circa 1987; cuid1882; 11083 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Pannaparayil, Thomas, undated; cuid1883; 11084 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Panwar, Shivendra, 1986; cuid1884; 11085 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Panzer, Marvin, 1950; cuid1885; 11086 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Papoulis, Athanasios, undated; cuid1886; 11087 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Parandelis, Raina, undated; cuid1887; 11088 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Parikh, Mihir, undated; cuid1888; 11089 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Park, Lawrence, undated; cuid1889; 11090 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Parker, Jack R., undated; cuid1890; 11091 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Parker, John C., undated; cuid1891; 11124 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Parry, John P., undated; cuid1892; 11125 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Parsons, Laura, undated; cuid1893; 11126 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Parsons, Richard D., undated; cuid1894; 11127 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Pascal, Donald D., 1973; cuid1895; 11128 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Patel, Rutton D., undated; cuid1896; 11129 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Patterson, Zahra, undated; cuid1897; 11130 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Pauling, Linus, undated; cuid1898; 11131 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Peale, Mundy I., 1963; cuid1899; 11132 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Pearce, Eli, 1974, 1986, 2000; cuid1900; 11133 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Pearlstein, Morton, undated; cuid1901; 11134 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Peck, Nicole, undated; cuid1902; 13396 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Penn, Lynn S., undated; cuid1903; 11135 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Penick, Joe E., undated; cuid1904; 11136 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Pennell, Knowlton E., circa 1955; cuid1905; 11137 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Penrose, Charles, undated; cuid1906; 11138 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Percy, undated; cuid1907; 11139 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Perez, John, undated; cuid1908; 11140 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Perl, Martin, 1993, 1998; cuid1909; 11141 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Perric, Lawrence J., undated; cuid1910; 11142 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Peshchansky, Vera, 1998; cuid1911; 11143 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Peterson, Beth, undated; cuid1912; 11144 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Peterson, N., undated; cuid1913; 11145 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Peterson, Roland, 1977; cuid1914; 11146 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Petit, Philippe, 1974, 1975; cuid1915; 11147 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Petrucci, S., undated; cuid1916; 11148 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Phillips, Donald, 1986, 2000; cuid1917; 11149 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Pickel, Paul F., undated; cuid1918; 11150 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Pierce, John Robinson, 1963; cuid1919; 11151 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Pierre, Charles, undated; cuid1920; 11152 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Pighi, Louis H., 1979; cuid1921; 11153 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Pignataro, Louis, 1975, 1978; cuid1922; 11154 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Pillai, S. Unnikrishna, 1998; cuid1923; 11155 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Pinkert, Dorothy M., undated; cuid1924; 11156 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Piore, Emanuel, 1967; cuid1925; 11157 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Pittle, Marvin S., undated; cuid1926; 11158 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Plympton, George W., circa 1900; cuid1927; 11159 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Poe, Alfred, undated; cuid1928; 11160 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Pollack, Myron I., undated; cuid1929; 11161 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Pomposello, Peter, undated; cuid1930; 11162 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Pond [Podnossoff], Jules, circa 1930; cuid1931; 11163 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Posner, N., 1986; cuid1932; 11164 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Post, Benjamin, undated; cuid1933; 11165 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - Potts, Charles E., 1937, 1954; cuid1934; 11166 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Prassas, Elena, undated; cuid1935; 11167 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Pratt, Edmund T., Jr., undated; cuid1936; 11168 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Preiser, Stanley, 1969, 1975; cuid1937; 11169 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Prekeris, Algimantas, undated; cuid1938; 11170 (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Press, Jack J., cuid1939; 11171 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Preston, Richard, circa 1998; cuid1940; 11175 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Prieto, Robert, circa 1999; cuid1941; 11176 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Prill, Stanley, 1963; cuid1942; 11177 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Privalsky, Chuck, circa 1968; cuid1943; 11178 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Prohaska, Dorothy, undated; cuid1944; 11179 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Proskauer, Eric S., 1978; cuid1945; 11180 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Protopapas, Angelos, undated; cuid1946; 11181 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Puccinelli, undated; cuid1947; 11182 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Puente, John, undated; cuid1948; 11183 (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Purcell, Joe, undated; cuid1949; 11184 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Pyke, Geoffrey Nathaniel, undated; cuid1950; 11185 (Box 6, Folder 189)
- Q, 11186
  - Qian, Jinghua, undated; cuid1951; 11187 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Quaglino, James V., undated; cuid1952; 11188 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Queen, Nathaniel M., 1958; cuid1953; 11189 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - de Queiroz, Marcio S., undated; cuid1954; 11190 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Quinn, John, undated; cuid1955; 11191 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Quirin, Edward J., 1966; cuid1956; 11192 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- R, 11193
  - Rabins, Michael J., undated; cuid1957; 11194 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Racz, Ernest, undated; cuid1958; 11195 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Radden, Frank, undated; cuid1959; 11196 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rader, Charlies M., undated; cuid1960; 11197 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Rader, Lloyd F., undated; cuid1961; 11198 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Radovic, undated; cuid1962; 11199 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ramberg, Eivind G.F., 1975; cuid1963; 11200 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Ramo, Simon, undated; cuid1964; 11201 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Rao, Bharat P., undated; cuid1965; 11202 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rasmussen, E. Hart, undated; cuid1966; 11203 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Rassier, Donald, 1984; cuid1967; 11204 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ratay, Robert, undated; cuid1968; 11205 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Ratner, Bruce, 2001; cuid1969; 11206 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Ratti, Umberto, undated; cuid1970; 11207 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Raymond, John H., Rev, circa 1871; cuid1971; 11208 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Rechtschaffen, Bernard, circa 1983; cuid1972; 11209 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Reed, undated; cuid1973; 11210 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Rees, R. [G.], undated; cuid1974; 11211 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Regna, Peter P., undated; cuid1975; 11212 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Reichle, Leonard F.C., undated; cuid1976; 11213 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Reid, undated; cuid1977; 11214 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Reidy, Michael, 1986; cuid1978; 11215 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Reilly, Henry J., Gen., undated; cuid1979; 11216 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Reiser, Arnost, 1980s; cuid1980; 11217 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Reissner, Hans Jacob, undated; cuid1981; 11218 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Reitenbach, Nicholas, circa 1998; cuid1982; 11219 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Rennie, Richard, circa 1996; cuid1983; 11220 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Riccio, Anna Maria, 1975; cuid1984; 11221 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Richman, Jana, cuid1985; 14790 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Richmond, Martin R., undated; cuid1986; 11222 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Rickels, undated; cuid1987; 11223 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Riseborough, Peter S., undated; cuid1988; 11224 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Rittvo, Steve, undated; cuid1989; 11225 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Robbins, 1952; cuid1990; 11226 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Roberts, Arnie, 1976; cuid1991; 11227 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Roberts, Martin E., undated; cuid1992; 11228 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Robinson, Guner Suzek, undated; cuid1993; 11229 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., undated; cuid1994; 11230 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Roden, Martin S., undated; cuid1995; 11231 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Rodriguez, Josephine, circa 1996; cuid1996; 11232 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Roess, Roger, undated; cuid1997; 11233 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Youth, undated; cuid1998; 11234 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Portraits, 1947, 1952, 1955, 1957; cuid1999; 11235 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Events 1940-1957, 1940-1968; cuid2000; 11236 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Events undated, cuid2001; 11237 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Rogers, Joel, undated; cuid2002; 11238 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Rogers, [Warren] L., Rev., undated; cuid2003; 11239 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Rogge, Herbert, undated; cuid2004; 11240 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Romanelli, Otto C., 1990s; cuid2005; 11241 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Romano, Frank, 1978; cuid2006; 11242 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Ronald, Mark, cuid2007; 13587 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Rorer, John, 1978; cuid2008; 11243 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Rosen, Bernard, undated; cuid2009; 11244 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Rosenberry, Walter S., undated; cuid2010; 11245 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Rosenthal, Myron, 1986; cuid2011; 11246 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Rosenthal, Saul W., 1955, 1967; cuid2012; 11247 (Box 7, Folder 62)